University of Connecticut, Office of Public Information (OPI) Records 1979.0011
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series VI: Biographical Files, 1957-1978
  - Loewy, Arnold
  - Loewy, Werner
  - Loika, William
  - London, Dr. Gardiner
  - Londos, Constantine
  - Long, Eugene
  - Lorenzo, Donald
  - Lowenstein, Sophie
  - Lovejoy, Frederick
  - Lubin, Barry
  - Lucas, Jack
  - Lucas-Lenard, Jean
  - Luciani, Adair
  - Machin, David
  - Maclennan, Dorothy
  - Madden, Gerald
  - Manigan, Francis
  - Madison, Patricia
  - Mahan, Erwin
  - Maher, Edward
  - Maher, John
  - Maier, Hans
  - Main, Eleanore
  - Maisto, Albert
  - Malone, Thomas
  - Mamer, John
  - Mandel, David
  - Mann, Bruce
  - Mann, A. I.
  - Mann, Wallace
  - Manzi, Rita
  - Marchok, Ann
  - Marcotte, Michael
  - Marcotte, Wayne
  - Marcus, Maeva
  - Maretzki, Thomas
  - Markham, Jean
  - Marlow, Wilma
  - Marshek, Kurt
  - Martin, Daniel
  - Martin, David
  - Mandell, Marion
  - Maseda, Maria
  - Masek, Karl
  - Massion, Charles
  - Masso, George
  - Matkin, Noel
  - Maxwell, James
  - Maybury, Catherine
  - Maroy, Mara
  - McCalister, C. N. Scott
  - McCaghy, Charles
  - McCan, Margaret
  - McCoy, James
  - MacLeod, H. Patricia
  - McCall, Joan
  - McCarthy, Ross
  - McClean, Michael
  - McConkey, Francis
  - McDougall, Edgar
  - McEwen, William
  - McFee, Wilhemina
  - McGillivray, Patrick
  - McIntire, Walter
  - McKain, Elizabeth
  - McKay, James
  - McKee, Clyde
  - McKee, kathleen
  - McKenna, Constance
  - McLaughlin, Robert
  - McLeavey, Dennis
  - McKinnon, Elizabeth
  - McLeod, Patricai
  - McLoughlin, Michael
  - McMann, William
  - McNallen, James
  - McPherson, Gertrude
  - McWilliams, Paul
  - Medlinger, Norman
  - Meigs, Walter
  - Menco, Hans
  - Menster, Michael
  - Mercer, Emily
  - Mercier, Dorothea
  - Mermin, Joel
  - Merrill, Stephen
  - Merritt, Edward
  - Merritt, Patricia
  - Meskin, Stephen
  - Mesnik, Eve
  - Messier, Elaine
  - Meyer, Joan
  - Meyers, Herman
  - Michener, Bryan
  - Milhench, marian (Box 6)
  - Miller, Ann
  - Miller, Audrey
  - Miller, Charles
  - Miller, Lawrence
  - Miller, Robert
  - Minden, Mary
  - Minghi, Julian
  - Minnum, Edward
  - Minutilo, David
  - Mirsky, Aron
  - Mitchell, John
  - Mitterling, Lloyd
  - Moeller, Fay
  - Moers, Ellen
  - Moffatt, David
  - Moffett, Russell
  - Mohammed, Hamdi
  - Molton, Rev. Warren
  - Momm, Albert
  - Monahan, Audrey
  - Monroe, Charles
  - Montgomery, James
  - Moudy, Harold
  - Montgomery, S. John
  - Monty, Percy
  - Mouty, Joycy
  - Moran, Conrad
  - Moravcsik, Michael
  - Morehead, R.
  - Morgan, John
  - Morgan, Max
  - Morgan, Thomas
  - Morrill, Shirley
  - Morrison, Thomas
  - Morse, Carole
  - Motock, Eugenia
  - Moulton, Verna
  - Moyer, Ralph, Jr.
  - Moyle, Wallace
  - Mullen, Harry
  - Munson, James
  - Murphy, William
  - Murstein, Dr. Bernard
  - Must, Gustav
  - Myers, Scott
  - Magyvary, Joseph
  - Nalwalk, Andrew
  - Nash-Adler, Priscilla
  - Nason, Doris
  - Natterstad, jerry
  - Neale, William III
  - Neary, Mary
  - Neill, Joseph
  - Nelson, Allan
  - Nelson, Donald
  - Nelson, Frederick
  - Nelson, Harland
  - Nelson, Randolph
  - Nelson, Thomas
  - Nemarich, Alfred
  - Nemergut, Paul Jr.
  - Neves, Anthony
  - Neville, Margaret
  - Neville, Richard
  - Neville, Robert
  - Newcomb, Bradley
  - Nicholson, Clara
  - Niculescu, Vasiu
  - Nielsen, Robert
  - Nienstadt, Helmut
  - Nofstker, Elizabeth
  - Nolan, Michael
  - Noll, Charles
  - Norman, Richard
  - Northern, Tamara
  - Norton, Mary
  - Nowotny, Hans
  - Noyes, Julie
  - Nutting, Bradley
  - O'Brien, Rev. James
  - O'Connell, William Jr.
  - O'Connor, Rose Marie
  - O'Donnell, Stephen
  - O'Malley, Thomas
  - Oestreich, Herbert
  - Ohrall, Richard
  - Oldenguist, Andrew
  - Olderman, Raymond
  - Oliver, Janet
  - Olsen, Clarence
  - Olson, Philip
  - Olson, Owen
  - O'Niell, Margaret
  - Onjeme, Andrew
  - Onkeliny, Claude
  - Orensteen, Roger
  - Orenstein, Harold
  - Orr, Harry
  - Orth, Paul
  - Osborn, Grant
  - Osborne, Richard
  - Osgood, Lawrence
  - Oshinsky, Leonard
  - Ossen, Jeffrey
  - Outersun, William
  - Overton, Paul
  - Owen, John
  - Oxley, Leo
  - Packer, Giles
  - Padovano, Anthony
  - Page, Joanna
  - Palazotto, Anthony
  - Palmer, Myrtle
  - Palmer, Priscilla
  - Paolino, Ronald
  - Paone, Arthur
  - Papeika, Janice
  - Parker, Donald
  - Papaconstantino, John
  - Paris, Duv
  - Parles, Carolyn
  - Parton, Charles
  - Patterson, Margaretta
  - Patty, Delbert
  - Pauli, Kenneth
  - Paulsen, Frank
  - Paulsen, Wolfgang
  - Paulson, David
  - Paulson, Morton
  - Paulus, Dieter
  - Payne, David
  - Pearson, Richard
  - Pease, Donald
  - Peck, James
  - Perret, Charles
  - Perez, Carlos
  - Perkins, Ruth
  - Perlman, Charles
  - Perna, Angelo
  - Perregaux, Paul
  - Perry, Herbert
  - Perry, Shirley, Joyce
  - Peters, Freda
  - Peters, Leonard
  - Peterson, H. Leroy
  - Peterson, Ralph
  - Peterson, Mayfield
  - Petro, Dominic
  - Petro, Stephen Jr.
  - Phelan, Mary
  - Phillips, John
  - Phillips, Leigh
  - Phillips, Richard
  - Phillips, Thomas II
  - Pichetti, B. W.
  - Piland, Richard
  - Pillai, N. Narayanu
  - Pinsky, David
  - Plastridge, Wayne
  - Plumb, John
  - Pocius Felix
  - Poirier, Dr. Paul
  - Polatnick, Jacob
  - Pullak, Otto
  - Pulonsky, Michael
  - Pomeroy, James
  - Ponasse-Lorris, Robert
  - Pool, Daniel
  - Pope, William
  - Potgreter, Martha
  - Potter, Capt. Frederick
  - Potter, Robert
  - Potz, Sgt. David
  - Poners, michael
  - Prakash, Inderjit
  - Prasuhn, Alan
  - Prior, George
  - Pritzkau, Philo
  - Prufumieri, Pierluigi
  - Prothro, (Watts), Johnie
  - Putzkel, Dr Max
  - Qadir, Abdul (Box 7)
  - Quade, Albert
  - Quina, James, Brian
  - Raab, Allen
  - Radigan, Patricia
  - Raffa, Joyce
  - Rahn, Perry
  - Raine, Brenda
  - Rainford, Dorothy
  - Ralson, Valery
  - Ramanauskas, Sigita
  - Ramanjaneya, G S.
  - Ramberg, Hans
  - Randolph, Dr W. Alan
  - Rangel, Vicente
  - Ranker, H. Joseph
  - Ransom, Dr. Philip
  - Rao, K Venkateswata
  - Rathgeber, Susan
  - Raymond, Elaine
  - Razim, Shmuel
  - Rea, R J
  - Recht, Michael
  - Reed, Diane Prezkop
  - Reed, Roland
  - Reed, William Jr.
  - Reese, Christine
  - Reeves, John
  - Reffner, John
  - Reich, Dr Alan
  - Reid, Parlane
  - Reilley, Robert
  - Reilly, William Robert
  - Reinfrank, Ralph
  - Reis, Robert
  - Resnick, Barbara
  - Reynolds, Beatrice
  - Reynolds, Charles
  - Reynolds, Maureen
  - Rice, David
  - Rice, Edmund
  - Rich, Anne
  - Richard, Clyde, Jr.
  - Richards, John
  - Rick, Margaret
  - Riihmaki, Barbara
  - Rinaudo, Peter
  - Rippey, Robert
  - Rhodes, Richard II
  - Rhomberg, Rudolf
  - Rich, Louis
  - Rigrodsky, Seymour
  - Robarts, James
  - Roberts, Helen
  - Robertson, Paul
  - Robin, Richard
  - Robinson, George
  - Robinson, John
  - Robinson, Leonard
  - Robinson, Patricia
  - Robinson, William III
  - Rodis, Nicholas
  - Rodowskas, Christopher
  - Rogers, Malcolm
  - Rogge, Elizabeth
  - Rollins, George
  - Roman, Victor
  - Ronfeld, Robert
  - Rooney, Geraldine
  - Rose, Benita
  - Rosenbauer, Wallace
  - Rosenwasser, Marie
  - Roser, Albrecht
  - Rosiene, Alan
  - Rosini, Lawrence
  - Rosinski, Edwin
  - Ross, Calvin
  - Ross, Raymund
  - Ross, Samie
  - Rottenberg, Daniel
  - Rothenberg, Albert
  - Roufosse, Theodore
  - Roupas, Theodore
  - Rouse, Jeanne
  - Rousseau, Joseph Jr.
  - Rowe, Edward
  - Rowe, H. Gerard, Jr.
  - Rowe, Lloyd
  - Roy, Rob
  - Rubin, Ben
  - Rubins, Edward
  - Ruegg, Alan
  - Russo, Richard
  - Ruth, Sara
  - Rutigliano, Sam
  - Ryan, Carolyn
  - Ryan, Judith
  - Sabino, Donald
  - Sakuda, James
  - Salas, Satunino
  - Saler, Benson
  - Salmon, E Dwight
  - Sampson, Ronald
  - Samuelson, H.
  - Samuels, Joseph
  - Sarenski, Joseph
  - Saver, Ferdinand
  - Sawick, Stanley
  - Sawyer, Elizabeth
  - Sawyer, Herbert Jr.
  - Saxon, Arthur
  - Scar, Janice
  - Schaefer, Ronald
  - Schattschneider, E. E.
  - Scheidegger, Kenneth
  - Schendel, Dr. Harold
  - Schimph, William
  - Schloss, Christine
  - Schmidt, Herman
  - Schoeplein, Kay
  - Schramm, Rogert J. Jr.
  - Schrueder, Edwin
  - Schulze, Richard
  - Schubert, Marcelle
  - Schuck, Robert
  - Schulze, Else
  - Schuster, John
  - Schwartz, Ruta
  - Schwartzbach, Irving
  - Schwink, Ilse
  - Scory, Jane
  - Scribner, William
  - Scrivener, Wayne
  - Seacrist, Joseph
  - Sedlock, James
  - Seagrave, Richard
  - Seaver, Stanley
  - Sechrist, Glenn
  - Seely, Samuel
  - Segroves, Kenneth
  - Sekanovich, Daniel
  - Selcow, Jay
  - Setlow, Peter
  - Selya, Roger
  - Sendich, Munir
  - Seretny, Linda
  - Serota, Daniel
  - Sespariak, Lawrence
  - Shabel, Fred
  - Shafer, nelson
  - Shapiro, Herman
  - Sharma, Nyantara
  - Shay, Barbara
  - Shea, Craig
  - Shea Thomas
  - Shedletsky, Leonard
  - Sheehan, Bernard
  - Sheehan, Kenneth
  - Sheehan, T. Joseph.
  - Shelly, Eugene
  - Shepard, Julia
  - Sherry, William
  - Shire, Steven
  - Shreve, Warren
  - Shipman, Carol
  - Shteyer, Arie
  - Shure, Robert
  - Siclari, Louis
  - Sidman, Robert
  - Silverman, Gerald
  - Silvers, Ronald
  - Simmons, James
  - Simon, Michael
  - Simonson, Heather
  - Sinclair, Keith
  - Sisca, Joseph
  - Sistare, Willard
  - Skipper, James
  - Skribanowitz, Peter
  - Slater, Paul
  - Slowinski, Emil Jr.
  - Slysz, William
  - Small, Audrey
  - Small, Donald
  - Small, Norman (Box 8)
  - Smith, Allan
  - Smith, Clifford Jr.
  - Smith, Daniel
  - Smith, Douglas
  - Smith, Ella
  - Smith, Fred
  - Smith, Gay
  - Smith, Hugh
  - Smith, Jerome
  - Smith, Joan
  - Smith, Maj. Linwood
  - Smith Mary
  - Smith, Paul
  - Smith, Robert F.
  - Smith, Robert S.
  - Smith, Ruth
  - Smith, Sidney
  - Smith, Stanley
  - Smith, Virginia
  - Smith, William III
  - Smolen, Joseph
  - Sneideman, Harvey
  - Snodgrass, R. J.
  - Snyder, Eugene
  - Snyder, Mary Ellen
  - Snyder, Patricia
  - Sofios, Nicholas
  - Soifer, Arian
  - Solomon, Morris
  - Solomon, Stuart
  - Song, J. A.
  - Soulos, George
  - Spann, Marcella
  - Spaulding, Kenneth
  - Spence, John Charles
  - Spencer, Vivian
  - Spengemann, Dr. William
  - Speyer, Joseph
  - Spitzer, Murray
  - Squires, John
  - Srivastava, Muni
  - Staffen, Patricia
  - Stage, Gerald
  - Stanley, Eugene
  - Stark, John
  - Stasunias, Casey
  - Stauvovsky, Linda
  - Steck, Robert
  - Steele, Karen
  - Steinberger, Clarence
  - Steinmann, John Francis
  - Stenzel, Bonnie
  - Stephan, Erich
  - Stephens, G. Ross
  - Stephenson, Lois
  - Stepita-Klauco, Matej
  - Stern, Jean
  - Stern, Robert
  - Stether, Henry
  - Stevens, Barbara
  - Stevens, Seth
  - Stevick, Philip
  - Stewart, Donald
  - Stewart, Kenneth
  - Stinchfield, Dr. Raymond
  - Stinson, John Jr.
  - Stires, Lloyd
  - Stockwell, Dr. Edward
  - Stoffel, Ronald
  - Stolman, Deenah
  - Stone, Sayard
  - Stoughton, Robert
  - Stoy, Robert Jr.
  - Strand, Gerald
  - Stratford, Eugene
  - Strauss, Manuel
  - Strauser, Richard
  - Taylor, Clifford
  - Taylor, Cynthia
  - Taylor, Delores
  - Taylor, Richard
  - Raylor, Thomas
  - Taylor, William
  - Teasdale, Barbara
  - Tewksbury, L. Blaire
  - Tenney, Henry
  - Thiebaux, H. Jean
  - Thomas, Dr. Anthony
  - Thomas, Daniel
  - Thompson, Diane
  - Thompson, Francis
  - Thompson, George
  - Thompson, Wendell
  - Tetreault, Alice
  - Thomas, Hugo
  - Thoms, Richard
  - Thorkelson, John
  - Thurston, Robert
  - Tichovskis, Heronims
  - Timoschenko, Gregory
  - Tingley, Katherine
  - Tippy, Kenneth
  - Todd, Christopher
  - Toedt, Theodore
  - Tong, Mary
  - Toniolo, Giovanni
  - Torgerson, Harold
  - Torpay, Judith
  - Totolis, Barbara
  - Toutellot, Gair
  - Trachtenberg, Stanley
  - Tracy, Derrick
  - Trail, John
  - Trask, Owen
  - Trautwein, Gerhard
  - Trench, John
  - Tipp, John
  - Troiano, Robert
  - Trovern-Trend, John
  - True, Nancy
  - Tryon, Ames Fox
  - Tucci, George
  - Tufts, Margaret Anne
  - Tumavicus, J. W.
  - Turcotte, Robert
  - Turner, Milton
  - Turner, Natalie
  - Tuthill, lt. Gordon
  - Twombly, Robert
  - Underwood, Larry
  - Unkel, Esther
  - Uzoaru, Benjamin
  - Vagell, John
  - Waddell, Fred
  - Wadsworth, Dwight
  - Waggoner, Neva
  - Walker, Colleen
  - Walker, Florence
  - Walsh, Robert
  - Walter, Ronald
  - Wampler, Eugene
  - Wanat, helen
  - Wandersee, Edward
  - Ward, Vincent
  - Wardwell, Douglas
  - Warner, Percy III
  - Warren, Alvin
  - Watt, Richard
  - Wenver, Edwin
  - Weber, Robert
  - Weckstein, Donald
  - Wedberg, Stanley
  - Weinberg, Sanford
  - Weinstein, Sam
  - Weinsberg, Fromu
  - Seiss, Richard
  - Weller, Leonard
  - Wellwood, Arnold
  - Welch, Betty Slocombs
  - Welch, Stephen
  - Wenus, Rosalio
  - Werboff, Jack
  - Whang, Robert
  - Wheller, William
  - Whitacre, W.
  - White, Edward
  - White, James, Leigh
  - White, Warren
  - Witney, Mary
  - Whittaker, Frederick
  - Wickney, Rugh
  - Widmoyer, Fred
  - Wiggins, William
  - Wignall, David
  - Wigton, George
  - Wilcox, Howard
  - Wilding, John Wilkes, Daniel
  - Willete, Robert
  - Williams, Carolyn
  - Williams, Clarence
  - Williams, Edward
  - Williams, Henry
  - Williams, Joan Dr.
  - Williams, Robert
  - Williams, Walter
  - Wills, Franklin
  - Wilson, Barry
  - Wilson, Constance
  - Wilson, Col. Franklin
  - Wilson, Gary
  - Wilson, M. Glen (Box 9)
  - Wilson, John Oliver
  - Wilson, Dr. Marian
  - Wilson, Martha
  - Wilson, O. Meredith
  - Winters, Hilda Glasgow
  - Wipfler, Heinz Carl
  - Wise, Col. John
  - Wogan, Michael
  - Wolfe, Dale
  - Wolfson, Iris
  - Wolkonski, Rochelle
  - Wood, Charlotte
  - Wood, David
  - Wood, J. Stuart
  - Woodhull, George
  - Wootton, Dorothy
  - Wortman, Robert
  - Wosenski, Fredrick
  - Wright, Gene
  - Wright, Phillip
  - Wu, Henry
  - Wverth, Dieter
  - Wulf, Ronald
  - Wyman, Edgar
  - Yarbrough, Jean
  - Young, Andrew
  - Young, Robert
  - Yost, S. William
  - Young, C. Gilbert
  - Younger, Jean
  - Zebian, George
  - Zorski, Henry K.
  - Zoukis, Christo
  - Zuboff, Arnold
  - Zurier, Robert
  - Zwerling, Stephen
- Series VII: Morgue Files, 1963-1984
  - 1963-1979 (Box 10)
    - American Association of University Women
    - Association of Governing Board of Universities and Colleges
    - Boys and Girls State, 1967-1981
    - College of the Virgin Islands
    - Constitution Oak
    - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities
    - Energy crisis
    - Hampton Institute Exchange Program
    - Hurricane Belle
    - UConn inauguration
    - Merger, 1979 UB and UC
    - Miss Connecticut
    - UConn news clips
    - Occasional papers
    - Orientation for UConn employee
    - Patricio, Rui, 1970
    - People
    - Permanent Commission on the Status of Women
    - Power outage
    - Radiation, 1974-1975
    - Selective service; draft
    - Slaying victim, Paul Klein
    - Storrs shopping center
    - Swan Lake
    - Teaching and Learning Committee
    - Rocco Testa Case
    - United State Information Agency
    - University reorganization and development
    - University of Bridgeport
    - Vice Presidents, UConn
    - Visiting Lecturers
    - Visiting professors
    - Water problems
    - Waugh
    - Weatherley slaying, 1969-1970
    - Wellness center
    - Winter, 1977-1978
    - UConn Foundation, 1968-1979
    - UConn Foundation Intern Program
    - Alumni Association, 1971-1979
    - Alumni Association; Annual Alumni Day
    - Alumni Association; Connecticut Day
    - Alumni Scholarships (Box 11)
    - Outreach Program
    - Faculty housing
    - Faculty, promotions of
    - Faculty/Staff Assistance Program
    - University professors
    - Toward an Allied Health Career Today (TAConnecticut)
    - School of Business Administration
      - Center for Real Estate and Urban Economic Studies, 1977-1979
      - Center for Insurance Education and Research, 1968-1979
      - Seminar on property and casualty insurance, School of Insurance
      - Stamford MBA Program
    - School of Education
      - Sports and Leisure Studies, 1968-1979
      - Reading-Language Arts Center
      - Northeast Community Education Center, 1975-1978
      - Henry Barnard Visiting Fellows
      - Gentry School of Education Building Dedication
      - Center for Open Education
      - Faculty
      - Adult Basic Education Institute
    - School of Engineering (Box 12)
      - American Society of Civil Engineers, Connecticut section
      - Fairfield University, School of Engineering, Arts-Engineering Program
      - Civil Engineering, 1968-1979
      - Civil Engineering reports
    - School of Family Studies, 1968-1979
    - School of Fine Arts, 1975-1978
      - New England String Quartet, 1980
      - New England String Quartet, 1974-1979
      - Laurel String Quartet
      - Connecticut Yankee Marching Arts Workshop
      - Puppeteers of America Festival, 1970 August 16 - 21
      - Nutmeg Summer Playhouse, 1977-1979
      - Graduate School degrees, 1977
      - Graduate School degrees, 1978
      - Graduate education and research, U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services: grants
      - Ford Foundation Grant (Box 13)
      - Eastman Kodak Company Grant
      - Graduate education and research, Connecticut Research Commission Grant
      - Graduate education and research, 1968-1975
      - Graduate education and research: corrections program
    - Health Center
      - Visiting professors
      - Legionnaire's disease research, 1976-1977
      - Dedication
    - School of Law
      - Tiernan case
      - Legal realist
      - Moot court competition
      - Law review, 1968-1975
      - Legal clinic, 1976-1979
    - Regional campuses
      - Avery Point, 1965-1967 (Box 13)
      - Avery Point, 1968-1979
      - Stamford, 1963-1976 (Box 14)
    - College of Liberal Arts and Sciences Chemistry, 1963-1979
      - American Cyanamid lectures
      - Requests for English majors booklet
      - English 101
      - Foreign language-Romance & Classical Languages, 1968-1979
      - National defense
      - Pershing Rifles
      - Military Day
      - Air Force ROTC
      - Center for Slavic and East European Studies, 1976-1979
      - Center for Italian Studies
      - Sociology, 1968-1979
      - Urban semester
    - School of Nursing (Box 15)
    - School of Pharmacy, 1973-1976
    - School of Social Work, 1968-1977
    - Center for Human Resource Planning and Utilization
    - LSD research
    - Psychology building
    - International Cheerleading Foundation
    - Summer jazz clinic
    - Courses by newspaper
    - Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO
    - Connecticut State Employee Association, CSEA conference
    - International Association of Machinists Leadership School
    - Graduate Engineering Program
    - New England Training Center for the Deaf
    - Institute of Public Service, 1975-1977
    - Connecticut Government /IPS Newsletters
    - Connecticut Town and City Finance Personnel Conference
    - Development Administrators Training Program, 1974
    - Development Administrators Training Program, 1976
    - Grand List and tax rates
    - News briefs, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - News sources directory, 1976-1977
    - News sources, 1974-1975
    - News sources directory, 1972-1973
    - News sources, 1970-1971
    - Public Service, Institute of
    - Reorganization of Public Information Office, 1974
    - ROTC
    - Salaries
    - Searex
    - Security
    - Social Sciences Data Center
    - Social Work, School of
    - Society for Cross Cultural research
    - State colleges
    - State scene
    - Story leads: press tour, 1966 -1980 September
    - IPS
    - General Assembly Pre-session Legislators Conference (Box 17)
    - Housing Code Administration Conference
    - Municipal Training Program
    - School for Connecticut town clerks
    - Ski slope
    - Student affairs and services: registrar's office, 1970-1976
    - Student Commissaries, Department of
    - Lester Shippee hall
    - Harriet Stowe dormitory, 1979
    - Student affairs & services: Student Facilities Task Force report
    - Student leaves
    - United Towers Organization (UTO)
    - Amateur Radio Club, WILXV
    - Blue Bike Program
    - Commuters' Union
    - Coalition
    - College Bound Day
    - Campus community carnival
    - CONTAC Black Student Magazine
    - Demonstrations
    - Marijuana, 1977
    - National defense training: military ball
    - New England Minority Women Administrators (NEMWRA)
    - Outmates, Inc.
    - Pakistan Society of Connecticut
    - Parachute club
    - Students plant-in
    - Puerto Rican Student Movement (PRSM)
    - Racism on campus
    - Rathskeller
    - Renaissance Fair
    - UConn Ski Racing club
      General note
      [3 PAGES MISSING FROM ORIGINAL FINDING AID]
    - Awards and Scholarships (Box 18)
      - Inter-racial Scholarship Fund of W. Hartford
      - William Kinnard, Jr. Scholarship
      - Phillip Lauter Foundation Scholarship
      - John Livieri Memorial Scholarship Fund
      - Joseph Loughlin Memorial Scholarship
      - Mansfield Volunteer Association Scholarship
      - Sears & Roebuck Foundation
      - WILI Scholarship
      - Walter Williams Scholarship Fund
      - Presidential Scholars
      - Honors Program, 1964-1979
        - Alpha Epsilon Phi
        - Alpha Zeta Omega Fraternity
        - Archons Honorary Society for Men
        - Beta Alpha Psi
        - Chi Epsilon, National Civil Engineering Honorary Society
        - Beta Sigma Gamma Fraternity
        - Eta Kappa Nu, Honorary Electrical Engineering Society
        - Kappa Delta Pi, honorary fraternity
        - Kappa Kappa Psi
        - Mortar Board
        - Phi Kappa Phi, 1968-1979
        - Phi Lambda Upsilon
        - Phi Kappa Tau
        - Pi Sigma Alpha
        - Phi Sigma Delta
        - Phi Sigma Kappa
        - Pi Tau Sigma, honorary Mechanical Engineering Fraternity
        - Sigma Pi Sigma
        - Sigma Theta Tau
        - TKE Chi Phi Fraternity
        - Tau Delta Sigma
    - Jorgensen Auditorium, 1979
    - NERAC, 1968-1977
    - Women's Center, 1975-1979
  - 1974-1984
    - Alumni office (Box 19)
    - American Can Co., UConn Foundation
    - Commencement degree list, 1985
    - Catalog requests
    - 3 Cen. Speakers Centennial File, 1980-1981
    - Centennial celebration
    - Annual Report, university
    - Annual Report, 1981
    - Annual Report, 1983
    - Annual Report to Governer
    - Athletics, Division of
    - Black Studies
    - Board of Governors
    - Board of Higher Education
    - Board of Higher Education (cont.)
    - Bachelor of General Studies
    - Bakke case
    - Ernest Boyer
    - UConn briefs
    - Business Administration, School of
    - Civic Center roof collapse
    - Collective bargaining
    - Blanche Collins
    - Commencement, 1983
    - Commencement press materials, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Commencement, 1985
    - Coordinating council
    - Connecticut Public TV
    - Connecticut Magazine
    - CONN PIRG
    - Economic Development, State Dept. of
    - Senior Development staff
    - Development Committee staff
    - Editorial Review & Assignment Board
    - Fact Digest, 1977
    - Fact Digest, 1978
    - Fact Digest, 1979, 1980-1981
    - Fact Digest, 1981
    - Fact Digest, 1982
    - Fact Digest, 1983-1984
    - Financial Aid letter
    - Food services
    - Higher Education, Commission on
    - Historical report
    - In Service training
    - Inner college
    - Inauguration
    - Inauguration, John DiBiaggio
    - Laurel Club
    - Legislature, State of Connecticut
    - Maps, UConn
    - Massachusetts, University of
    - National Womens Studies Association
    - New England Board of Higher Education
    - Marine Science Institute, 1968-1974 (Box 21)
    - Institute of Water Resources, 1971-1974
    - Institute of Material Science, 1968-1974
    - Institute of Material Science, 1975-1979
    - Yearender's, 1967-1976
    - Yearender's, 1977
    - Yearender's, 1978
    - Yearender's, 1979
    - Yearender's, 1975-1976
    - Dean's List